Long have I awaited
this moment, human filth.
With the Subterranean and
Deep Sea kings gone,
the Terror Lizard Clan can
at last reclaim rulership of the Earth!
Now leading target towards  point Bravo.
Roger.
We are inbound and on schedule.
We'll be on top of Bravo shortly.
UNPARALLELED PERIL
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration ☹
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
And who are you?
Hello? What is it?
What do you mean, come back?!
You're the one who said
some weirdo monster was waking up
and flew me out here!
Weirdo...?
That's right.
I was just about to start.
Listen well!
I am the Ancient King.
– As ruler of the dinosaurs
– "Trouble?" So what?
– who once ruled this planet,
– It's not my problem.
– I stand above all other lifeforms.
– Hey, shut it!
Can't you see
I'm on the phone here?!
I'm so tired of this.
Who's he think he is,
ordering people about?
Are you done?
What's with the chin?
Trying to be scary?
Should I be intimidated?
Act brave while
you still can, little runt.
Runt?! How dare you!
Ah, so you aren't helpless!
But if you intend to destroy me,
a giant meteor is about the only way.
Fine. I'll do that then.
Don't make me laugh.
How about another
300,000,000 year nap?
Fist of Flowing Water, Crushed Rock.
It goes something like that.
Want to try?
You both look like quick learners.
I bet you'll get the hang of it  in no time.
This is the cool thing you said
you wanted to show us?
A sales pitch?
I'll pass. You do it, Genos.
No, I will pass too.
What I seek is not
the art of self-defense,
but absolute destructive power.
You punks!
You dare mock our fighting style?!
I, Charanko, the top disciple,
challenge you—
I give up!
Is he really your best?
Yeah...
I heard your dojo was
full of skilled fighters.
Well, one of my disciples went wild.
He beat my most skilled students
so badly they're all
out of commission.
The rest got scared and quit.
He's that strong?
What's his name?
Garo...
He was my top disciple at the time,
but I gave him a good
beating and expelled him.
You must pack a punch, old man.
Hey! This is the famed hero "Silverfang!"
Class S hero, rank 3.
He toys with opponents
as he flows like water,
then delivers a blow like
a raging river smashing huge rocks!
A master of martial arts!
You only became
a hero recently, right?
You'll regret taking
Master Bang lightly!
Enough, Charanko!
Do not disgrace us.
Saitama is many times
stronger than me.
Master, you can't be serious...
Mr. Silverfang!
The Association sent me.
An emergency summons has been
issued to all Class S heroes!
Please come to
Association Headquarters.
Oh! Is that you, Mr. Genos?
Since all Class S heroes have
been summoned, please come too.
Is it threat level Dragon?
Here we go...
Charanko, look after the dojo.
Be careful, Master!
If Class S is being summoned,
they may need your help too, Master.
Will you come?
I will...
since I got nothing to do.
HERO ASSOCIATION HQ
Oh ho, Silverfang!
It's been a while, Atomic Samurai.
I knew you'd come.
And this is the cyborg Genos and...
Hm? Who's this?
This is the Class B hero Saitama.
His exceptional talent will one day
place him atop Class S, I'm sure,
so we asked him to come.
Hi, middle-aged hero dude!
Put 'er there!
No handshakes.
I acknowledge only the strong.
Once you've climbed up to Class S,
I'll greet you properly.
Besides, I'm not middle-aged yet.
I'm only 37.
37 isn't middle-aged?
I had no idea...
Hey, who brought
a Class B nobody along?
Don't you think it's beneath us?
And even if you were invited,
a polite person would decline. The nerve!
I bet you're only here
for some creepy reason
like getting close to
us Class S heroes.
You disgust me. Leave.
What's with this sassy...
lost child?
That is Tornado. Class S, rank 2.
– "That"? I am not an object!
– She defeats monsters
with her psychic powers.
She is an ESPer.
Oh yeah...?
It appears everyone is here.
We should join them.
Hey...
Stop ignoring me!
CLASS S  RANK 17
PURI-PURI PRISONER
Maybe this will be my chance
to get closer to Genos...
GENOS
CLASS S  RANK 16
It must be serious.
Almost everyone is here.
CLASS S  RANK 15
METAL BAT
Demon or Dragon, bring it on!
CLASS S  RANK 14
TANK-TOP MASTER
Saitama? The name rings a bell...
FLASHY FLASH
CLASS S  RANK 13
CLASS S  RANK 12
WATCHDOG MAN
Somebody farted.
CLASS S  RANK 11
SUPERALLOY BLACKLUSTER
They're all checking out
my guns. Hell yeah!
CLASS S  RANK 10
PIG GOD
CLASS S  RANK 9
DRIVE KNIGHT
CLASS S  RANK 8
ZOMBIEMAN
No one looks particularly enthusiastic.
And does that pig ever stop eating?
CLASS S  RANK 7
KING
CLASS S  RANK 6
METAL KNIGHT
ABSENT
CLASS S  RANK 5
CHILD EMPEROR
Rank 1's a no show again?
I was hoping to see him.
CLASS S  RANK 4
ATOMIC SAMURAI
Is Silverfang going to take
those youngsters on as students?
CLASS S  RANK 3
SILVERFANG
So... why are we all here?
Who knows? I had to drop everything
and then got kept waiting for two hours.
CLASS S  RANK 2
TERRIBLE TORNADO
CLASS S  RANK 1
BLAST
ABSENT
CLASS B  RANK 63
SAITAMA
Can I have some tea?
My apologies for being late.
We do not know the whereabouts
of Metal Knight or Blast,
nor can we reach them.
No sense waiting any longer,
so let's begin this emergency meeting.
You can call me Sitch.
I'm with the Association.
I will be briefing you.
Let's get right down to brass tacks.
You heroes are here because
you're the best of the best.
And now...
We're asking you to save the Earth!
However, even with your Class S skills,
there is no guarantee of survival.
Walking away also takes courage.
Should you choose to do so now,
you will retain Class S status.
But those who stay and hear me out
will not be allowed to walk away.
You will be confined here
until the incident is over
in order to avoid a general panic.
Are you all willing to hear this?
Whatever's going on,
it better be worth calling
all of us here.
I skipped out on my little sister's
piano recital for this.
If it's a load of crap,
I'm gonna tear
this whole building apart.
Like you could do that
with that skinny stick.
Yeah? How 'bout I bust
your head open instead?
If you think you can,
go on and try, pillbug head!
Hurry up and get on with it.
Otherwise Mr. Pompadour here
is going to die.
Hey, bobby pin,
you siding with the girls?
The great seer, Madame Shibabawa,
is dead!
Shibabawa? Was she killed?
No.
While looking into the future
for the next six months,
she became agitated and
had a coughing fit.
She popped a cough drop
in her mouth
and ended up choking on it...
I get it!
So we have to figure out
how to prevent disasters
without the help of predictions.
That's the focus of this meeting.
No. Madame Shibabawa
has only been able to predict
a handful of disasters.
Excuse me!
Hey, you there.
Who's this Shibabawa? A hero?
You don't know?
She's a seer.
A great one at that.
She correctly predicted earthquakes
and monster attacks.
We've gotten through many crises
without Madame Shibabawa's predictions.
But even so, we provided a bodyguard
and gave her special treatment.
Yes, because her few predictions
were 100% accurate.
The crux of the problem, though,
is her last, greatest prophecy.
Even as she choked on
that final cough drop,
she managed to leave this note.
It is a prophecy that will
absolutely come to pass.
Here it is!
Can you read it?
– Th-The earth...
– ...is in trouble?!
THE EARTH IS IN TROUBLE
What? That's so dumb.
Can I go? I have cram school.
I know you are a prodigy,
Child Emperor,
but if you cannot grasp the danger,
it reveals how immature you still are.
What'd you say?!
Listen up!
Madame Shibabawa's predictions
are 100% accurate!
She has predicted many
catastrophes in the past.
A few of them resulted in
the loss of countless lives.
But not once did Madame
Shibabawa use the word "trouble."
Something more dangerous than a Dragon
level catastrophe or monster is on its way.
And it will occur...
...in the next six months!
Okay, but we've no idea
when in the next six months.
Yeah, hard to plan for that.
You are correct.
But I want you all to be ready
for a fight in the next six months.
In the next six months means...
it could be tomorrow, or even today.
That's true. Who are you, anyway?
Good thing I'm here.
The building is under attack!
That's impossible!
This is the Hero Association HQ!
A formidable fortress, to be sure!
Time to attack.
Hawk, Eagle, Falcon, Kite!
– Yar!
Wipe out these so-called heroes
and the land will belong to us!
We will dive straight in!
Follow me, the Sky King!
Father...above us...
Escape...
Me, the Sky King, killed like
some worthless insect.
Who could have—
What was that?
– Who knows?
– It flew, so we killed it.
That is good.
Duty, to protect ship.
Emergency power activated.
What was that?
What's going on out there?
I don't know.
All communications have been cut off.
Damn it...
Impossible!
Dad!
We're okay now. Grab on to me.
That's the way.
Good job.
What is this?
There are survivors?
– Ship, failed to kill all.
– Then we kill.
That is good.
Get away now!
You think I don't sense
your thirst for blood?
I accompanied Master Atomic
and was waiting for
the Class S meeting to end,
only to meet thunder
and destruction.
Is this your doing?!
Destruction levels at 99.8%?
City A has been destroyed in an instant!
Who could have known her prediction
would come true this soon?!
Hey! Why was this building spared?
We assigned Metal Knight
to construct this building.
That's why it's stronger
than the average shelter.
So that's why there're no windows.
We should go outside and see.
To be sure it's the prophecy.
Master! Will you—
Master...
That's big!
Are they aliens?
So that's what blew
the city to pieces.
Go back to...
your planet!
A militant creature.
Also cautious.
Hurry. Let us hurry and kill.
That is good.
Can it be killed?
Each of its strikes is lethal!
I can't beat this thing...
Such a weak species.
Easily killed.
That is good.
It's splitting?
Damn, not now...
I will dispose of this.
You handle the rest.
Very well.
I will go kill those that ran.
That is good.
I—
Master!
Iairon, you okay?
You know, your left arm...
Master! Swords have no effect
on this monster.
Forget me! Retreat!
Outta my way!
Iai! The path of the sword does
not end for you yet!
Stop bleeding!
Yes, Master!
So there is a life-form on
this planet that can fight.
Excellent!
Try to withstand our invasion!
Planet, eh? You from outer space?
And you got friends up
in that floaty toy?
Yeah, that's it.
I doubt you alone have the power
to do all this to the city.
Atomic Samurai, count us in.
You the bastard that smashed
this town?!
And if I am?
For all the beautiful men
you killed...
I claim vengeance!
Each separate attack must
be delivered with intent...
...to kill!
Dark Angel
Flash!
Issue an evacuation warning to
City A and all neighboring cities.
Right now!
And expand the System M vitals
monitor to cover all of City A.
We need an accurate
count of the survivors.
What's the threat level?
"Dragon," without doubt.
No...
This might be "God."
Four Class S heroes can take care
of the enemy on the ground...
The problem is that.
We can't reach it.
Any aircraft would be
shot down in seconds.
King, you're one of
the top fighters in Class S.
Give us your take.
King, Class S rank 7.
Said to be the strongest man
on Earth,
and I see he is well respected
by the other heroes...
There's nothing I can do.
It's too high in the sky.
There's no way to attack it.
But the mysterious craft
is currently dormant.
We should use this opportunity
to call in Metal Knight.
What the—?! That's pathetic!
Aren't you supposed
to be the strongest man?
Hey, Tornado.
– If you piss King off, he'll kill you.
– This city's been blown away,
and you're just going
to give them a free hand?
Unbelievable!
Well forget it!
I'll take care of this myself.
Wait, I will go too.
I do not know how effective I can be,
but I will attack from the ground.
Maybe you didn't hear me.
I said forget about it!
Take it easy, Genos.
I understand how you feel,
but if you piss her off, she'll kill you.
Very well...
There is no need to
team up anyway.
Master has already boarded
the enemy ship.
Whether this is the prophecy or not,
there's not a single evil
Master cannot defeat.
If such an evil existed,
then I assume the human race
would have perished long ago.
Well done making it this far, intruder!
But this is the end.
You see, there is no way
you can defeat me, Groribas!
My Acid Breath will melt you away!
Isn't it about time the boss
showed up?
Well, if he's alive...
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
NEXT
Episode
THE DOMINATOR OF THE UNIVERSE
I, Groribas, control this preview!
I perfected some new moves.
Now I have like 20!
But I couldn't show them off,
because, you know,
they killed me off first!
Next time on One-Punch Man:
Episode 11,
"The Dominator of the Universe."
It's your fight now, Lord Boros!